Guide to the Martin Poll Papers MC.200
New York University Archives
- Series VI: The Dain Curse (1978), 1974-1978
  - Slides -- Malachy McCourt, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Slides -- N. Addison, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Slides -- Private Eye, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Slides -- Temple, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Slides -- Watch Mounting, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - The Sound Shop, Inc., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Straight, Beatrice, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Stunts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Teleplay, Part I, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Teleplay, Part II, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Teleplay, Part III, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Teleplay, Part III Master - First Version, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Teleplay, Parts I-III Final Master 2/21/1978 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Teleplay, Parts I-III Final Master 2/21/1978 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Title Registration, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Union Agreements, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Vehicles Breakdown, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Weiss, Nat - Promotion, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Widetracks, Voiceovers (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Widetracks, Voiceovers (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Widetracks, Voiceovers (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Xerox Corporation, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Series VII: Stunt Seven (1979), 1977-1979
  Arrangement
  Series VII is titled "Stunt Seven" because the majority of production materials refer to the project by this title. However, the film was released under the title The Fantastic Seven.
  - Analysis, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Budget, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Budget 2/19/1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Budget, Based on First Draft, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Budget, Second Draft 12/18/1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Call Sheets, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cash Flow, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Casting, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Caterer, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CBS, General, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - CBS Meeting 10/26/1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Charts, Circa 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Contact Sheets, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Contact Sheets and Film, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Memos, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Crew List, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Crew List, Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cue Sheets, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Daily Production Reports 1/28 - 3/2/1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Dialogue Only Cassette Tape, Reel 1-3 and 4-6, Undated (Box 25)
  - Dialogue Only cassette Tape, Reel 7-9 and 10, Undated (Box 25)
  - Dialogue Only Cassette Tape, Reel 1-4 and 5 to 8, Undated (Box 25)
  - Dialogue Only Cassette Tape, Reel 9-10, Undated (Box 25)
  - Equipment, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Film Binder, 1 of 2, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Film Binder, 2 of 2, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Foreign Distribution, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Insurance, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Inventories, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Line Scripts, Acts I-III, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Line Scripts, Acts IV-VI, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Line Scripts, Revisions, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Locations, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Log Sheets, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Marine Corps, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Music Cues, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Permits, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Portrait (Photograph), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Post-Production Schedule, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Pre-Production, Chronological File, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Presentation Books, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Production Forms, Lists, and Documents, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Production Reports, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Production Schedule, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Publicity, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Research, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Screening, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Screenplay, Final Master 3/2/1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Screenplay, Final Draft Master 12/17/1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Screenplay Revisions, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Screenplay, Second Draft Master 12/18/1978 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Screenplay, Third Draft 1/2/1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Screenplay, Third Draft 1/2/1979, Martin Poll's Copy (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Serialization, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Serialization, Originals, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Simmons, Stanley - Costume Designer, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Slides -- Barroom Brawl, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Slides -- Christ Connelly Choice, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Connelly, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Slides -- Connelly and Brodsky Climbing, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Slides -- Connelly and Lloyd, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Slides -- Fantastic 7, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Slides -- Glider Shot and Hang Glider and Plane Trans, L.A., Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Slides -- Good and Others, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Slides -- Helicopter and Brittany Connelly, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Slides -- Helicopter and Connelly-Brittany and Sommer-Masnel, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Slides -- Head Bashing on Board, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Slides -- Kill (Judy Landers), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Slides -- Lloyd and Brodsky, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Slides -- Morgan Brittany at Swimming Pool, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Slides -- Others, 1 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Slides -- Others, 2 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Slides -- Others, 3 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Slides -- Others, 4 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Slides -- Others, 5 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Slides -- Others, 6 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Others, 7 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Slides -- Others, 8 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Slides -- Others (Bill Macy), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Slides -- Others (Connelly and Brittany), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Slides -- Others (Connelly and Broadsey), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Slides -- Others (Eke), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Slides -- Others (Fantastic Seven), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Others (Linda Beatie), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Slides -- Others (Morgan Juanine), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Slides -- Others (Morgan Showering), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Slides -- Others (Party), 1 of 2, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Slides -- Others (Party), 2 of 2, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Slides -- Others (Shots of FBI Men), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Slides -- Others (Sommer/Macwell), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Slides -- Others (Soon Teck Oh), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Slides -- Others (Soon-Teck Oh and Group Planning), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Slides -- Others (Party-Seagren and Blond, Haskell and Brunnette), Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Slides -- Swiming Pool, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 1 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 2 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 3 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 4 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 5 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 6 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 7 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- Unlabeled, 8 of 8, Circa 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - "The Specialists" by David Shaw, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Story Ideas, New, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Story Ideas, Original, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Stunt People, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Title Reports and Credits, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Travel, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Nighthawks (1981), 1978-1980
  - Arding and Hobbs, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "A.T.A.C." Script Notes, Martin Poll, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Badalato, Bill - Production Supervisor, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bielecki, Stanley, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Billing Information, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bintliff, Russell - Police Consultant, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bintliff, Russell - Police Consultant, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bintliff, Russell - Police Consultant (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bintliff, Russell - Police Consultant (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Budgets (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Budgets (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Call Sheets and Daily Production Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Casting (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Casting (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Casting, London, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Contact Sheets, 1 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Contact Sheets, 2 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Conter, Jim - Director of Photography, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Conti, Tim, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Credits, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Crew List, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Daily Production and Progress Reports, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Davenport, Nigel, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Deal Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Distribution, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Distribution, International Cinema Corporation, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Editing Notes, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Emerson, Keith, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - English Crew File, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Greenburg Associates, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Hauer, Rutger, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Heim, Alan, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Howard, Trevor, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Insurance, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Inter-Office Memos, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Letters to and from Cast and Crew, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Locations, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Looping 12/30/1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Khambatta, Persis, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Malmuth, Bruce - Director, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Music, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Name Clearing, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Nelson, Gary, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Non-Principal and Other Deal Memos, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Numbers, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Paris and New York City Police, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Post-Production, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Press Kits, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Production Budget, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Pre-Production Notes, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Promotion Schedules, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Publicity (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Publicity (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Dar, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Roosevelt Island Complaint, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Screening, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Screening Reports, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Screenplay, "A.T.A.C.", undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Screenplay, Final Draft "Hawks", undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Screenplay, Final Draft "Dragons", undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Screenplay, Final Draft "The Attack", undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Screenplay, Revised Draft "All God's Creatures" 10/24/1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Screenplay, Revised Draft "The Attack" 10/15/1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Screenplay, Revised Final "Dragons" 12/18/1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay, Revised Final Draft "Dragons", undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Screenplay, Revised Final Draft "The Attack" 12/3/1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Screenplay, Revised Final Draft "All God's Creatures" 10/24/1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Screenplay, Revised First Draft "A.T.A.C.", undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Screenplay, Second Draft "A.T.A.C." 4/6/1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Shooting Schedule, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Dick - Makeup Artist, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Story Summary "A.T.A.C.", 1979 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Status Reports, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Stallone, Sylvester, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Telexes, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Thompson, Hilaire, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Timing Breakdown, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Titles, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Touboul, Serge - Production Manager in France, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Translations, Foreign, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Production Company and United Artists, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tramway to Roosevelt Island, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - United Artists and Layton Productions, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Universal Studios Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Wagner, Lindsay, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Weitzner, David - Universal, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - White, David - Production Manager in London, 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Billy Dee, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Willoughby, Bob - Photographer, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Xerox Complaint, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Series IX: Arthur the King (1985), 1979-1983
  - Actor Contracts - Drafts B - H, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Actor Contracts - Drafts L-W, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Andrews, Anthony, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Atari, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Berger Literary Agreement, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Bielecki, Stanley - Publicist, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Billings to CBS, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Bills sent to Yugoslavia and London from New York Office, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Breakdown Sheets, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Brittenham, Skip - Attorney, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Budgets, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Martin Poll's Copies, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Budget 6/18/1982 per Conversation with D. White (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Budget 10/1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Casting, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Casting, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Casting, Fenton, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Casting, Martin Poll's Notes, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Casting, Martin Poll's Notes and Pictures, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Cannon, Dyan, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - CBS, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - CBS Agreement, unsigned 2/27/1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - CBS Agreement, signed 5/11/1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - CBS Contract dated 12/16/1978, signed by Martin Poll 5/9/1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - CBS Delivery Requirements, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - CBS Press Releases, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - CBS Program Practices, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Chulay, John, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Chulay, John - Martin Poll's Notes, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Contact Lists, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Contact Sheets, 1 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Contact Sheets, 2 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Continuity No. 1 (Binder), 1 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Continuity No. 1 (Binder), 2 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Continuity No. 1 (Binder), 3 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Continuity No. 2 (Binder), 1 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Continuity No. 2 (Binder), 2 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Continuity No. 2 (Binder), 3 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Continuity No. 2 (Binder), 4 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with CBS, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Costume Breakdown, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Crew, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Crew List, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Czechoslovakia, Miscellaneous and Photos, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Director, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Distribution, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Donner, Clive - Director, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - EMI America, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Emmy Nomination, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Final Cast List, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Final Credits, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Graphics, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Grinstaff, Doug, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Gross, Charles - Composer, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Jadran Studios, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Karp, David - Screenwriter, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lists and Other Producation Materials (Binder 1), 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lists and Other Producation Materials (Binder 2), 1 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Lists and Other Producation Materials (Binder 2), 2 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Lists and Other Producation Materials (Binder 2), 3 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Location Photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Marhell, Bob, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Martin Poll's Files, Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Martin Poll's Notes, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Merlin and the Sword, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Meyer, Bob, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Music, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Opticals, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Photographs and Other Images, Circa 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Pig-Faced Woman, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Post-Production, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Posters and Drawings, Circa 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Posters, Drawings and Other Miscellaneous, Circa 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Prime Time School Television, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Production Budget, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Production Budget/Loose Report, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Production Notes, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Production Notes and Other Miscelleneous, Circa 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Program Practice Notes, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Progress Reports (Post-Production Binder), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Proposal, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Publicity, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Research, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Research, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Research, 1979-1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Research, 1 of 2, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Research, 2 of 2, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Research, Stonehenge, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Revisions, 11/1982 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Romania, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Screenplay, Act One Revised 6/25/1982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Screenplay, "Arthur Rex", Part I "Save the Queen", undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Screenplay, Final Revised 7/16/1981 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Screenplay, Final Revised 6/25/1982 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Screenplay Graphic Materials (Binder), 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay, Master Copy, Revised 8/12/1982 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Screenplay, Part I Revised 9/22/1980 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Screenplay, Part I Revised 10/10/1980 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Screenplay, Part I, Revised Draft 9/22/1980 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Screenplay, Part I "Save the Queen" 6/21/1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Screenplay, Part I "Save the Queen" 1/1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Screenplay, Part II, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Screenplay, Part II First Draft 7/9/1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Screenplay, Part II First Draft 7/31/1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Screenplay, Part II "Voyage to Avalon" 10/22/1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Screenplay, Part II "Voyage to Avalon" 11/1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/26/1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/19/1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/23/1982 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/29/1982 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Screenplay, Revised 6/29/1982 including Third Revision 9/9/1982 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay, Revised 7/31/1982 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Screenplay, Revised 8/4/1982 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Screenplay, Revised 8/12/1982 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Screenplay, Revised 10/25/1982 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Screenplay, Revised 1/2/1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Screenplay, Revisions 9-10/1982 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Screenplay, Revisions 11/1982 - 2/1983, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Screenplay Revisions via Telex, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Screen Tests, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Shooting Schedules, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Shuler, Lauren, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sketches, Circa 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Special Effects Budget, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Special Effects Budgets, no dollar amounts, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Telexes to and from Czechoslovakia, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Telexes to and from Hungary, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Title Registration, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - WGA Arbitration, Wyles/Karp, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Wyles, J. David - Screenwriter, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Yugoslavia, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Series X: Gimme an F! (1984), 1983-1984
  - Badalato, Bill - Producer, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Balance Sheets, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cash Flow Projections, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Casting, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cheerleader Research, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Continuity Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Credits, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Crew List, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Deal Memos, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Directors, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Distribution, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Hammer, Jan - Music, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Hart, Jim - Screenwriter, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Insurance, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Justman, Paul - Director, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kopelson Option, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Ledgers, General, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Merritt, Steve - Choreographer, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - New Scenes, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Opening in South Florida, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Picture Book, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Production Budget, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Publicity Material, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Revised Script Structure 9/15/1983 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Screenplay 5/24/1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Screenplay 6/1/1983 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Screenplay, B Draft Revised 8/25/1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Screenplay, Master Revised 8/25/1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Screenplay Notes 8/31/1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Screenplay, "The Big Cheer" Final Draft 12/8/1983 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Screenplay, Revisions 12/16/1983 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Screenplay, Revisions 12/28/1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Screenplay, Second Draft Master Copy 10/12/1983 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Screenplay, Second Draft Revised 10/6/1983 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Script Changes, "The Big Cheer" 1/3/1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Shooting Schedule, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Show Cost Reports, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Supplemental Documents, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Synopsis, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Title Registration, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Unions, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Warner's Requisition Request, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Series XI: Projects, 1968-1977
  - Miscellaneous Materials, 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Screenplay, "All the Angels" First Draft by Evan Jones, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Screenplay, "Mrs. Fritz" by James E. Colaneri, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)